<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nolan Brubaker, Software Developer</title>
    <link>http://nbrubaker.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nolan Brubaker, Software Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://nbrubaker.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playing Codenames remotely</title>
      <link>http://nbrubaker.com/horsepaste/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nbrubaker.com/horsepaste/</guid>
      <description>Download the Zoom client using the first link at the top.
Join the meeting by clicking a Zoom meeting link!
To play, go to https://www.horsepaste.com
If you&amp;rsquo;re not sure how to play, watch the rules explanation.
Some etiquette If you&amp;rsquo;re joining, please devote most of your attention to the call Try to use a headset - it makes it much easier for you to hear others, and for others to hear you </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Look For In A Company</title>
      <link>http://nbrubaker.com/hireme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nbrubaker.com/hireme/</guid>
      <description>Hopefully, this page will help you get to know me a little better, and help us both judge if your company and I would be a good fit.
First and foremost, I seek to work at places and projects where I am a force multiplier: working on things that make others more effective or efficient. I want to help others work better. I feel most comfortable working on tools that help other developers, but this isn&amp;rsquo;t a hard requirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://nbrubaker.com/growing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nbrubaker.com/growing/</guid>
      <description>Growing as a software engineer I&amp;rsquo;ve recently taken on my first tech lead role, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking time to reflect on what that means. I think a huge part of being a tech lead is growing your team, and recently I got the question, &amp;ldquo;How do I know what subject areas are available? What should I do in order to get promoted into more senior positions?&amp;rdquo;
My opinion is that a huge part of moving up in seniority is being able to deal with ambiguity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
